neuroleadership.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy - NeuroLeadership Institute

### **NeuroLeadership Institute Privacy Policy**

Neuroleadership Institute, Inc. (“NeuroLeadership/NLI”), recognizes the importance of your privacy. This online privacy policy explains our data collection, processing and usage practices.  It also describes your choices regarding your personal data collected by NLI.  If you have additional questions about NeuroLeadership’s data collection practices after reading this notice, please contact us at [privacy@neuroleadership.com](mailto:privacy@neuroleadership.com).

#### 1\. Information NLI collects from you

NeuroLeadership, by itself or via third party providers, collects personally identifiable information such as names, job titles, company name, phone numbers, email addresses, country, state and city from visitors who voluntarily input such information in response to prompts we have placed at various points on our website and other links provided to you by NLI. NeuroLeadership also will collect name and e-mail addresses from the e-mails you send us or if provided in response to our marketing and quality control materials. Some of our third party providers automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our site, such as the type of browser you are using, your general location, or the domain name of your Internet service provider. They also collect aggregate information on the site pages our users visit. The data we hold is kept securely and only accessed by authorized personnel.

Computer data containing no personally identifiable information will be used only for internal business purposes and then discarded.

#### 2\. Legal Basis for collecting and Processing Your Personal Information.

The majority of the personal information collected by NeuroLeadership is provided by you voluntarily, for example when you sign up to join a mailing list, register for an event, or respond to a survey link and is therefore collected with your permission. The remaining personal information is collected for NeuroLeadership’s legitimate business purposes as outlined below:

**2.1** The reasons that we process your Personally Identifiable Information include the following:

  * To protect users. 
    * We use the customer information and other personally identifiable information we maintain about users and their use of  NLI services and products, including registration information, as follows: 
      * To help us identify users.
      * To help us prevent unauthorized persons from accessing customer information and other personally identifiable information and the product features that we make available to specific users for their use.
  * Measurement: 
    * To understand how often users use parts of our services and products. 
      * By understanding more about users and their use of the products, we can better meet user needs and determine how other product features could be of value to users and to improve services and products.
    * Provide customers with anonymous aggregated data that gives an understanding of the measureable impact of NLI services and products.
  * To tell you about new or enhanced services and/or products.
  * We use customer information and other personally identifiable Information to respond quickly and efficiently to user needs.
  * To improve and develop our information, Products and services. 
    * Every Product feature that we offer is designed to reflect the ways users actually use the Products.
    * We collect and analyze information about Product use so that we can tailor new types of information, products and services to meet user needs.
  * Email Updates: 
    * Once a user completes the registration process, NeuroLeadership may keep the user updated by email on important news and events concerning NeuroLeadership, Product features, and other information that NeuroLeadership deems relevant.
    * By accepting this Privacy Policy and by using any Product, each user agrees that NeuroLeadership may contact the user by email with respect to NeuroLeadership and any aspect of the products whatsoever.

NeuroLeadership will not sell information it collects. We may disclose your personal information to our third party providers in order to process data for the above mentioned purposes, to third parties who work on our behalf to service or maintain business contact databases or if required by law.

The data gathered also will be shared appropriately with our offices in the United States, Europe, Asia and Australia.

#### 3\. Cookies

Like many websites, we may use “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s device containing information about the user’s visit. The Site uses both 1st party cookies (which are set by the Site being visited) and 3rd party cookies (which are set by a server located outside the domain of the Site). We use cookies to keep track of logon ID as well as track of pages viewed. You can change your user settings in your browser to prevent us storing cookies on your device. You can find out how to do this, and find more information on cookies, at: [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### Some of our Third Party Cookies include:

  * Google Analytics cookies: we use these cookies to track information about a user’s visit, including the IP address of the visitor, time and duration of visit, pages viewed, visit source/referring site and time zone. We use the information to check the usefulness of our website and help us improve it and so enhance visitor’s experience of its visitors. You can view the Google Privacy Policy here: www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
  * Marketo Analytics: We use Marketo to help us measure how you interact with the You can view here: https://documents.marketo.com/legal/cookies/

Your consent to cookies

By agreeing to this policy you consent to the use of cookies by us as described above.

#### 4\. Protecting Personal Information

NeuroLeadership will store personal information as required to meet legal and regulatory requirements or as additionally needed in accordance with this policy.

#### 5\. Retention/Deletion of Personal Information

We retain personal information that you provide us as long as we consider it potentially useful in contacting you about our services, improving our services or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, and then we securely delete the information. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request, as described in “Opting Out and Unsubscribing” below.

#### 6\. Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information

Upon request NeuroLeadership will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If you provide us with your Personal Information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:

  * To review the user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that your user information not be used to contact you or processed in any other manner
  * To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use
  * To withdraw consent and request that your user information be deleted from our records
  * To opt out of being solicited by NeuroLeadership or third parties

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at privacy@neuroleadership.com. We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken.

If you object to our processing of your personal data, you have the right to complain to the data protection authority (“DPA”) in the country where you reside, where you work, or where an alleged infringement of data protection laws has taken place.

#### 7\. Children

This website is not intended for use by children. We understand the importance of protecting children’s information, especially in an online environment, and we do not knowingly collect or maintain information about children.

#### 8\. Agreement and Changes

NeuroLeadership may revise this policy or any part of it at any time. We suggest you review the policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the website and/or continued provision of personal Information to us will be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Policy last updated 9/12/2018**
